[
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”’ Add my Microsoft Account?",
		"response": "Absolutely! Let's navigate to Account settings... ğŸ§­",
		"action": "ms-settings:privacy-accountinfo"
	},	
	{
		"question": "ğŸ¤“ Ready to set up a PIN",
		"response": "Absolutely! Let's dive into Sign-in settings...",
		"action": "ms-settings:signinoptions"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”„ Check for Windows updates",
		"response": "Right away! I'll initiate the update check...",
		"action": "updateCheck"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”„ Restore backups",
		"response": "Of course! Let's navigate to Windows Backup settings...",
		"action": "ms-settings:backup"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ—‘ï¸ Uninstall an App",
		"response": "Sure thing! Opening Windows Apps Uninstaller...",
		"action": "ms-settings:appsfeatures"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”„ Reset my system",
		"response": "Need a fresh start? Let's get you sorted! ğŸ”„",
		"action": "systemreset"
	},
	{	
		"question": "ğŸ–¼ï¸ Change desktop wallpaper",
		"response": "Absolutely! Let's change it up!",
		"action": "changeWallpaper"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ’» Tweak Windows appearance and performance",
		"response": "Let's head over to Performance Options together.",
		"action": "SystemPropertiesPerformance.exe"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸŒ— Toggle Dark/Light mode",
		"response": "Join me as we switch themes...",
		"action": "toggleThemeMode"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ›¡ï¸ Create a Restore point",
		"response": "Your system is now on the safe side! Restore point created.",
		"action": "createRestorePoint",
		"powershellCommand": "$desc = 'BloatynosyAI Restore'; Checkpoint-Computer -Description \"$desc\" -RestorePointType \"Modify_Settings\"",
		"description": "Create a restore point",
        "category": "Plugin"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ§¹ Clean up storage",
		"response": "Time to tidy up! Running Storage Sense...",
		"action": "runStorageSense",
		"description": "Run improved version of cleanmgr.exe to clean-up your system",
        "category": "Plugin"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸªŸ Check Windows version",
		"response": "You're currently rocking Build: [buildNumber]. Looking good! ğŸ‰",
		"action": "showWindowsVersion"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ’¾ Check available disk space",
		"response": "Need to check disk space? Let's take a peek...",
		"action": "showDiskSpace"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ“¸ Take a screenshot using SnippingTool",
		"response": "Screenshot captured and sent to clipboard. Ready for the next step!",
		"action": "takeScreenshot"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”” Show autostart apps",
		"response": "Opening Task Manager to the autostart tab...",
		"action": "switchToAutostartTab"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸš€ Show Processes with High RAM Usage",
		"response": "Let's take a look! Listing processes...",
		"action": "showHighRamProcesses"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ›¡ï¸ Run a quick scan in Windows Defender Security",
		"response": "No problem! Running a quick scan...",
		"action": "runWindowsDefenderScan"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ® Show Chris Titus tool in action",
		"response": "Absolutely! Interpreting PowerShell script...",
		"action": "runPSFile",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\ChrisTitusAppHandler.ps1",
		"description": "Launch the Chris Titus app for a demonstration",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/ChrisTitusAppHandler.ps1"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”’ Enable Secure AutoLogon on Windows",
		"response": "Sure thing! Running PowerShell script...",
		"action": "runPlugin",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\AutoLogonHandler.ps1",
		"description": "Configure Windows for secure AutoLogon with enhanced security measures.",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/AutoLogonHandler.ps1"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ§¹ Clear Windows Event Logs",
		"response": "Mission accomplished! The logs have been successfully cleared",
		"action": "runPlugin",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\ClearEventLogsHandler.ps1",
		"description": "Clear all Windows event logs to free up space and maintain system performance.",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/ClearEventLogsHandler.ps1"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”„ Restore Windows Inbox Default Apps",
		"response": "Certainly! Initiating PowerShell script...",
		"action": "runPSFile",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\plug.restoreInboxApps.ps1",
		"description": "Restore the default inbox apps on Windows using the Get-AppxPackage command if they were previously removed.",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/plug.restoreInboxApps.ps1"			
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸš€ Remove Microsoft OneDrive app",
		"response": "Of course! Interpreting PowerShell script...",
		"action": "runPSFile",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\OneDriveHandler.ps1",
	    "description": "Uninstall the OneDrive app from your system",
        "category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/OneDriveHandler.ps1"		
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ›¡ï¸ Disable telemetry for third-party apps",
		"response": "Sure! Disabling telemetry for selected apps...",
		"action": "runPSFile",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\plug.appsPrivacyTemplate.ps1",
		"description": "Disable telemetry data collection for third-party applications Media Player, Office, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome Software Reporter Tool, CCleaner Monitoring, Dropbox and Google Update service",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/plug.appsPrivacyTemplate.ps1"		
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ”’ Disable specific Windows telemetry services",
		"response": "Certainly! Disabling selected Windows services...",
		"action": "runPSFile",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\plug.disableServices.ps1",
		"description": "This will disable following services: diagnosticshub.standardcollector.service, DiagTrack, dmwappushservice, lfsvc, MapsBroker, NetTcpPortSharing, RemoteAccess, RemoteRegistry, SharedAccess, TrkWks, WbioSrvc, WMPNetworkSvc, XblAuthManager, XblGameSave, XboxNetApiSvc, ndu",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/plug.disableServices.ps1"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ§¹ Remove default inbox apps in Windows",
		"response": "Sure! Removing default inbox apps...",
		"action": "runPSFile",
		"scriptPath": "plugins\\plug.removeDefaultApps.ps1",
		"description": "Removes default inbox apps in Windows, including Cortana, 3D Builder, Bing apps, Microsoft Office Hub, Minecraft, Skype, Xbox apps, and various third-party apps.",
		"category": "Plugin",
		"githubURL": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Winpilot/main/extensions/plug.removeDefaultApps.ps1"
	},
	{
		"question": "â™»ï¸ Empty the Recycle Bin",
		"response": "Got it! Emptying the Recycle Bin...",
		"action": "runPS",
		"command": "Clear-RecycleBin -Force"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸŒ Check my IP Address",
		"response": "Absolutely! Checking your public IP address...",
		"action": "ipCheck"
	},	
	{
		"question": "ğŸ› ï¸ Tweak privacy and system",
		"response": "Switching to CoTweaker...",
		"action": "plugCotweaker",
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ® Tweak gaming settings",
		"response": "Switching to CoTweaker...",
		"action": "plugCotweaker",
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ’© Debloat my system",
		"response": "Time to clean up! Switching to Decrapify...",
		"action": "plugDecrapify"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ“¦ Install an app using winget",
		"response": "Let's make it happen! Switching to WingetUI...",
		"action": "plugWingetUI"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ” Search for AI on my system",
		"response": "Absolutely! Let's see what AI features are enabled.",
		"action": "plugCopilotless"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ‘‹ Show me a Clippy tip",
		"response": "You're in luck! How about a tip? ğŸ“",
		"action": "plugClippySupreme"
	},
	{
		"question": "â™»ï¸ Restart Windows Explorer",
		"response": "No problem! Restarting explorer.exe...",
		"action": "shell",
		"command": "taskkill /f /im explorer.exe && start explorer.exe"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ“ Change Taskbar alignment to left",
		"response": "Sure thing! Taskbar aligned to the left.",
		"action": "shell",
		"command": "reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarAl /t REG_DWORD /d 0 /f"
	},
	{
		"question": "ğŸ“ Align Taskbar to center",
		"response": "Taskbar aligned to center.",
		"action": "shell",
		"command": "reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarAl /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f"
	},
	{
		"question": "â• Add Widgets Button to Taskbar",
		"response": "Adding Widgets Button to Taskbar...",
		"action": "shell",
		"command": "reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarDa /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f"
	},
	{
		"question": "â– Remove Widgets Button from Taskbar",
		"response": "Removing Widgets Button from Taskbar...",
		"action": "shell",
		"command": "reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarDa /t REG_DWORD /d 0 /f"
	}
]
